Guide to the University of Pittsburgh Women's Studies Program Records, 1970-2005 UA.15.26
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Subject Files, X.
  - Carolyn Sylvander, WHA Radio Interviews, October 18-December 8, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Clara Bell Duvall Education Fund, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Feminist Network Project, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Feminization of Power Campaign, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Haven Inc. Brochure (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Hillary Clinton Letter on the United Nations, Women's Conference One Year Later, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Mid-Atlantic Women's Studies Association, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Mother Root Journal, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - National Council of Jewish Women, 1995-1997 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - National Council for Research on Women, 1995-1997 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - National Women's Studies Association, 1995-1997 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Pittsburgh Gay and Lesbian Community Center, 1986-1997 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Posters from TABS, Journal of Aids for Ending Sexism in School, 1978-1984 (Map-case 3-5, Oversize 1)
  - Pro-Choice, 1981-1995 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Pro-Life, 1982-1995 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Sexism in Education, 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Sexism in Language, 1972-1977 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Western Pennsylvanians United for Choice, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Women and Blacks in Pittsburgh, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Women and Media, 1982-1990 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Women and Work, 1973-1991 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Women Artists, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Women Authors, 1978-1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Women in India, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Women in Science, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Women's Center, 1980-1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Women's Organizations, 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Women's Organizations, 1980-1998 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Women's Studies ISIS, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Women's Studies Library Collection Development, XI.
  This series includes information on the creation and efforts to devolop the Womens Studies Collection at Hillman Library.
  - Audio-Visual Material on Women at Hillman Library, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Women's Studies Collection Development, 1972-1978 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Women's Studies Microform in Hillman Library (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Women's Studies Recent Acquisitions at Hillman Library, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Women's Studies Reference List at Hillman Library, 1987-1995 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Women's Studies Resources at Hillman Library, 1975-1980 (Box 8, Folder 13)